A possible Red Flag prisoner is in our offices.
Cameron said that he and Nina had him subdued,
and now they're bringing him here.
I thought Sullivan wanted an approach and evaluate.
See if the man is an Alpha or any Red Flag connections.
Clearly things went another way.
So we still don't know what his ability is?
No.
Well, it's a good thing we got this thing up and running.
19, 68, 16, 7.
That's not your birthday, is it?
Super bowl III.
Jets beat the Colts 16-7.
Yeah, but you couldn't have been old enough to have been there.
I was six months old.
I even have a photo of my dad holding me while he was watching the game,
so that makes me a Jets fan for life, baby.
And we're coming. You see what we did last year, right?
Yeah, that's football, right, Bill? Uh, yeah, football.
Anyway, so we got bulletproof, polarized glass.
We've got industrial-grade surge suppressors, fire-retardant foam.
And the best part is we got an emergency lockdown, the whole office.
So the windows, doors, everything shut.
Now, if only we can get D.O.D. to buy us a new car.
Can they do that?
Oh, gosh, Bill, I-I don't know.
I've allowed this to go so far beyond what I envisioned for all of us.
Doc, you got to get over that. We're not longer just your patients.
We're a government asset.
What's the expression, dance with the devil in the pale moonlight?
You got to go with the flow, right? Isn't that what you always tell me?
Look, ever since that mess with Jonas Englin,
I've lost my ability-- I'm here, right? I'm good with it. You're good with it, so--
No, I'm not all that good with it. It's not who you are,
and the D.O.D. isn't happy either.
Actually, I'm trying to figure out a way to get the ability back.
You're a fine investigator, Bill, but as far as the government's concerned,
we are a group of Alphas.
Well, you're not an Alpha. You're still here, right?
- And besides, Doc... - Huh?
Jeannie and I are thinking about renovating the kitchen.
So, please, keep those checks coming. This isn't gonna work.
This isn't gonna work. They ignored my checklist. I made a detailed list.
Sleep gas dispensers and telepathy blockers and some automated gun turrets.
Gary, those things don't exist. Yeah, I like the old Bill better.
You'd take things seriously,
and your veins would pop out when things weren't right, and this isn't right.
Why aren't your veins popping out anymore? I don't have to worry about that anymore.
Why are you still here, then? You're not even an Alpha anymore.
If I wasn't here, you'd miss me, right?
You being gone and you being different are the same thing.
Whatever, Bill. Whatever.
???I got it.
Are you hearing me? What was that noise?
Check, over? Bill, Ten-four?
Uh, Rachel, this is not a police radio.
- You can speak normally. - Okay. I hear them.
They're in the elevator with Dr. Kern. All right, thanks.let's go
Sorry about this.
Were able to confirm any Red Flag connection?
We barely sat down before he got suspicious.
What about an Alpha ability?
I tried to push him, but it just didn't work.
I want to run some MRIs first,
then we can put him in the holding cell.
Let's move fast before he wakes up.
Doc, you okay?
Uh, yeah. It's just, um...
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==-
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
阿尔法战士第一季第09集
-=破烂熊字幕组=-
时间轴：葫芦娃
Please don't wake him up.
Relax, Rachel. You know I still have my gun,
and I am a better shot when I'm not all amped up.
You know, Bill, I was thinking,
if I dosed you with a mixture of adrenaline and steroids,
we might be able to jump-start your ability. Doc, I am not interested.
All that got me was issues, right? Marriage issues, work issues and--
No, I-I understand your concerns. Who needs it?
We might.
We all have our issues, but we're learning how to control them.
Yeah, well, I'm all in control now. Thank you very much.
All right, let's see what we have here.
Paperwork already? God, you're so motivated.
I used to ignore it and pretend it would go away, but it never did.
Cream, no sugar, right?
I pay attention.
I wonder what tipped Kern off to us. Guy's an obstetrician.
He sees happy couples all the time. I guess he didn't see that in us.
And what, we don't buy the whole happy-couple thing?
No, look, I'm not saying that.
Rosen thinks that it's a bad idea,
you and me.
Wait a minute. You told him?
Well, he's our shrink.
Why, is it because, um...
because I'm divorced and in A.A.?
Or maybe it's because I have a kid.
We work together. It would be unprofessional.
No, we do things in this job all the time that are unprofessional, and you know that.
That's not it.
He thinks that I'd be bad for you,
and...
He might be right.
Cam, I've screwed up every relationship I've ever had.
Me too.
So we're perfect for each other.
Hey, guys.
Um, Doc found something. We got a meeting.
Yeah, we're on our way.
How can Kern be blind? Because he has no optic nerve.
The MRI revealed something, uh, well, pretty interesting.
It's as if they never developed. So, even if his eyes were functioning properly,
as they appear to be, no visual data would ever reach his brain.
Which is why I couldn't push him. He couldn't see me.
Look, when things got ugly, that guy dodged around his desk, and he ran straight for the door.
There is no way he's blind.
Well, unless he's an Alpha, which I have some ideas about,
uh, but I need to run a few more tests.
So we're talking about a blind Alpha that's a baby Doc and a member of Red Flag?
Where's my phone? Who's got my phone?
Bill? Bill! Bill!
Gary, I've been here the whole time. What are you talking about?
Yeah, where'd you put my phone? Gary, I've been here the whole time.
Gary, your phone is right here. Oh, well, that's not okay.
People shouldn't be touching my phone. It was a gift. It's special.
Yes, okay, and it's back in your hands.
- It's fine. - Yeah. No, it's not, 'cause it's open to data files, and those are private.
Yes, Gary's phone is private. Please, no one is to touch it unless they have Gary's permission, all right?
Yeah, and the answer's no.
To get back to our case, the reason Dr. Kern is here--
D.O.D. suspects that he's been doing some sort of research,
and they are hoping that we can figure out why.
And more to the point, a radicalized Alpha
who is also an obstetrician, that's a disturbing thought to say the least.
Well, we cleaned out his office-- hard drive, cell phone, patient files.
Meds, vitamins, blood samples.
Which, Rachel, you'll take a look at? Yeah. That's great.
And, Gary, you will look into the cell phone and computer transmissions?
That's just data mining. People without abilities can data-mine.
Well, you know, we all can't do that.
- I can't do it, Gary. - Neither can I.
No, we all know that you are so much more than your abilities, Gary.
- You have very many talents. - I know. I'm amazing.
warning:human urine
My lucky day.
Gary?
Hello?
Who's there?
Did you call me? I'm working.
Do not disturb, that's my I.M. chat status.
I should get a sign.
Hey, Gary, were you just there by my office? Rachel, you're not making sense.
I told you, I'm working.
I work in my office.
Bill, will you remove the mouth strap? You sure?
Yes, I have the test results I need.
I just would like to speak with him.
Okay, whatever.
Let me tell you something... Happiness is a warm gun.
And mine is a Sig 226. You got me?
I want my lawyer. Yeah, and I want a Reuben sandwich.
I'll have my lawyer pick you up one.
Well, unfortunately, Doctor Kern, you're being detained because of suspected involvement
with a terrorist organization.
The only organization I belong to is the A.M.A.
So, what, Alphas, ability, Red Flag--
that means nothing to you?
Bill, will you take the cuffs off,
stand him up, and have him face the glass?
Get up slowly. Keep your arms up.
Turn around and face the wall, please.
What is this, a cavity check?
That's just as I thought...
sonar, echolocation.
- So he's like a bat? - Or a dolphin.
You can sit down now.
Very interesting. You have no optic nerves.
However, the audio-processing capabilities
of your brain, your voice box,
the chambers in your sinus passages
are all significantly enhanced. You're an Alpha.
But of course you already know that. This isn't going to end well.
Is that a threat?
Hey, Cley, Rosen and I are going to keep working with him,
and Rachel's nosing around through what we found in his office.
Yeah, Rosen thinks that he's probably said about as much as he's going to,
so why don't you come scoop him up?
All right, what, two hours?
From Knoxville?
All right, have a safe flight.
Doc, can we talk? I'm a bit busy, Cameron, can we--
No, it won't take long.
Look, I just wanted to say, um, me and Nina...
If you just give us a little space
and let us figure some things out for ourselves...
I'm only trying to look out for the both of you.
Well, I get that, but we're adults.
We get to make our own mistakes, so, please, just let it go.
I'd like to, but as your psychiatrist and your employer,
I don't think I can do that.
And I don't think you're in a place to make that decision.
Am I interrupting? I'm always interrupting.
I'm sorry, but I found something in the box I was going through.
It's important.
Here, look at these.
"Building blocks for a better baby."
Yeah, they're vitamins for pregnant women.
I decided to break one open and take a look inside-- you know, really take a look.
Rachel, what did you find?
DNA...
active human DNA inside the vitamins.
Active human DNA
introduced into a developing fetus
could cause multiple birth defects, severe mutations.
Yeah, that's what I was worried about.
Hold on a second. I smell blood...
in the hallway.
Nina. It just started bleeding.
I haven't had one of these since I was a kid.
Oh, gosh, look up. Are you dizzy?
- No, it's okay. - Headache or anything?
It was just a few broken capillaries,
nothing serious, but were you picking?
I don't pick.
Here, take this.
You'll be fine. Just clean it up, okay?
Yeah. Good.
Are you aware you have mitral valve prolapse--
three millimeters of displacement?
You just did an ultrasound of my chest.
You should get that looked at.
Well, I have a heart exam twice a year.
I'm monitoring it, but, uh...
thank you for your concern, though.
Like you, I took an oath...
do no harm.
I may be an Alpha, but I'm a doctor first. I hope you'll keep that in mind.
No harm.
What kind of doctor gives active human DNA
to pregnant women?
Someone who cares about the future.
Whose future?
You're aware of Renestrin--
new drug that allegedly prevents birth defects?
But what it really does is interferes with the fetal development
of more evolved children.
What you're really saying is it prevents babies from being born as Alphas.
Consider my special vitamins the counteragent.
Are you planning to distribute your counteragent
all by yourself?
Can any of your team read minds?
Well, I guess there's some questions that aren't meant to be answered.
Dr. Rosen, I know what's going to happen next.
Men with guns will whisk me away to some government facility.
That would be a tragic, tragic error.
Well, I'm afraid the real tragedy
is you choosing to join a terrorist organization.
Red Flag isn't as monolithic as you think it is.
Well, regardless of its scope, you and your friends tried to assassinate me.
Fringe elements, radicals, not representative of the mainstream.
You know, it's amazing how often people use that term--
"fringe elements."
Occurs to me that the I.R.A.,
P.L.O., K.K.K.--
all fringe elements
whose very existence depends upon the support
of their mainstream fellow travelers.
I've read your field reports, Doctor.
You advocate a future where Alphas and normal humans
cooperate for the common good.
That's the future I want.
We should be working together, comparing notes.
You're inviting me to join Red Flag?
I'm afraid I don't meet their entry requirements.
I see a time coming soon
where the unenhanced will be able to join our cause.
That's where you belong.
Dr. Kern, if you're willing to disclose
what exactly it is you're up to,
I'm willing to intervene on your behalf.
Impasse.
I'm disappointed for you, Doctor.
Well...
I'm not the one going to Binghamton.
What makes you think I am?
Bill? Hicks?
Come on, guys, this better not be a joke.
This guy's holding out on us.
Any ideas how we break him down?
- Well, he's sonic guy, right? - Yeah.
Maybe it's time we pull out the Captain & Tennille's
Muskrat Love.
- Sonic warfare. - Mm-hmm.
Yeah, it's been known to work.
Just remember, anything we force him to listen to we got to hear it as well.
Trust me, we used the same trick on detainees in Bagram.
Still feel sick every time I hear Copacabana.
- I love that song. - Oh, come on.
I do. It's one of my favorites.
You hear that? Gary screwing with the computers again?
I can't get in the system.
It seems like it's running some sort of keypad retrieval.
- Have you seen Rachel? - No, not lately.
She's not in her office, and no one's seen her for a half hour.
Why don't you scream for her?
Yeah, I did, okay? She's gone.
- Rachel? - Rachel?
Rachel, if you can hear us, say something. Nothing, nothing.
There's something wrong with the security cameras.
Gary, come here, come here. Show me what you're looking at.
- Pull it up on the monitor. - Okay, it's glitchy.
Give me Rachel's office an hour ago.
Something's making it glitch. Yeah.
Okay, okay, there she is,
in her office going over the stuff from Kern.
Can--can you fast-forward?
It's glitchy, though. It's glitchy.
Okay, wait, wait. Here, here. And then she leaves.
Oh, no, wait, wait. I found her.
20 minutes ago. There.
There.
Hicks! Nina!
Stay here. This way.
Rachel!
Rachel?
Rachel, where are you?
This is the last place she was seen on camera, right?
Yeah. Rachel!
- Oh, my God. - What?
Over here.
It's blood, and it--
I got blood here, too. Okay, and these look like drag marks, right?
Starting over there. No, they start here.
Well, she couldn't have just evaporated. What the hell?
Rachel, where are you? Rachel?
Hey, take a look at this.
Was this like this when we moved in?
What are you doing?
Where's Rachel? Rachel?
Which one's Rachel, the tall one?
- The other woman. - I never met her.
You can do more with your sonar than just find things.
I'm chained to a table.
I can't run around abducting people with my voice.
Besides, my hearing is quite good.
The number of heartbeats on this floor hasn't changed since I awoke.
How many are you hearing?
Do we really have to play this ridiculous game?
There are eight. There have always been eight.
Yours, mine, and the six members of your team, I assume.
We haven't been properly introduced.
Dr. Kern, there are only six of us, that includes Rachel and myself.
Plus you, that's seven.
What?
Have things...
Have things gone missing around your office...
Strange sounds,
computers turning on randomly,
people sensing someone nearby without ever seeing anyone?
You have an unwelcome guest.
What are you saying,
That--that Rachel's been kidnapped
and that the person is still here in the building?
Let me solve your problem. Let me help you, or we're all dead.
Why should I believe anything you say? All right, don't. Don't.
But one member of your team is down already.
Ignore me, things will only get worse.
Let me out!
Before it's too late, let me out!
You need to let me out! I'm the only one who can keep us alive.
Don't need to hear that. I don't trust that guy for a second.
Look, I searched the entire office again-- still no Rachel.
And we got nothing to go on except what Kern is saying.
I can't wait for Cley to show up and get this guy out of here.
Not until we find Rachel.
Yeah, I think we-- we should at least consider what Kern is saying.
An intruder would certainly explain some of the strange things that have been happening here.
Hey, Doc, earlier today, I thought I was imagining something, right?
But I felt that someone was watching me.
I turned around, and there was no one there. Exactly, Bill.
That is called proprioception.
It's one of the ways we have of processing the million bits of information
in our environment around us.
Like you said, if you find yourself in a room full of people, you sense something.
Then you feel compelled to turn around, and they're looking right at you.
That's our proprioception at work. So our proprioception says someone's here,
but our eyes say there isn't.
Yes, well, unlike Rachel,
when we're looking for something,
we rely on our vision.
But vision can be deceptive.
How many dots do you see? Two.
All right, now hold this with your right hand.
All right, close your left eye.
Look at this dot and move the paper slowly towards you.
One of the dots just disappeared. Into your blind spot.
You've all heard of one. We all have one.
It's a hole or gap in our visual landscape
which exists because of the way our brains are wired.
And we might be dealing with an Alpha who can exploit this phenomenon.
Okay, let's say that there is an Alpha here, right,
that does that-- how do they get into that gap? Bill, I don't know.
They might be able to send a signal that swells the optic nerves,
thereby expanding collectively the blind spot
and move into it so nobody can see them.
I still don't buy it. I mean, there's cameras everywhere.
An Alpha might be able to mess with our brain, but how does he get past the cameras?
The cameras are glitched. Someone's made them glitchy.
There's dropped frames and time lag. Enough to get around without being seen?
Yes, yes. But it's only our cameras.
It's only the cameras inside this building.
Yeah, the camera across the street
looks into this building every 15 minutes.
And that's why I won't go to the bathroom at three minutes after
or at 18 or 33 or 48, yeah. Gary, Gary, Gary, come on.
Okay, watch this.
Who is that woman? Wait. Who's that woman?
Hicks, behind you! Where'd she go?
I can't see her.
Cameron? Hicks, what happened?
I never even saw her. This isn't good. That's a lot of red.
Get a pressure bandage on that right away.
Come on, she's activating the blast door!
Password's been changed.
Well, all the phones aren't working either or the Internet.
Yeah, and Rachel's missing. Hicks is on the D.L.
Even if Cley gets here in time, he couldn't get in. Don't worry about that now.
Maybe Gary can override the lock system. That's worth a try.
Ah, stupid security glass!
Gary?
Gary, what are you doing? I'm using two chairs.
- Gary, no. - I tried one chair.
Now I'm using two. - Gary, Gary--
No, Dr. Rosen, I used one chair.
- I'm speaking to you, Gary. - Yeah, let me use the chairs.
I need your help. Will you come with me?
- I am helping. - Come with me, please.
It won't kill you,
but no bouncing off the ceilings for a few days, okay?
Well, I'm glad someone paid attention
during the first-aid class Harken made us take.
Okay, come on, come on. We got to find Rachel.
I'll get Rosen to give you some pain pills.
Addict.
Sorry.
Not good for you.
Don't care.
that witch took my phone
- What witch? - The witch!
That's the word my mom uses when she's angry. She uses another word, too.
She took Rachel, and she took my phone.
The bitch got my gun.
- I think it's from-- - That sounded like my gun.
- Bulletproof glass... - Gary.
Excellent idea.
- It's crackly. - Gary.
Do you have my phone? Do you have Rachel?
Gary, Gary, I need you to see if you can get the computer systems back online.
- Don't leave his side. - Got it.
- Cameron. - Rachel--I'm on it.
- This just in my gut. - Hey, hey, where is she?
Where's blind spot girl?
You mean the person who just tried to shoot me? Or free you.
I say "day," you say "night."
We're never going to find common ground like this.
Yeah, you want common ground, why don't you start with a name?
Griffin.
Her name is Griffin, but I suspect it's a nom de guerre.
Red Flag considers her an unsanctioned variable.
What exactly does that mean?
Someone who sells their services to the highest bidder
but supports no cause, has no allegiance.
A person should believe in something, don't you think?
You two I respect. Even though you're wrong,
at least you're loyal to a cause greater than yourselves.
So you're saying that she's just a mercenary doing anything for money?
My ability can be extremely useful in finding her,
not to mention your missing compatriot, Rachel.
- Rachel, yes. - I don't think so.
Then you guys waltz out of here laughing your asses off.
Good try.
Does it look like I'm laughing? Griffin's after me.
She'll do whatever it takes to get me, including killing all of you.
Look, either you're a target, or you're an accomplice,
but either way, you're staying right where you are
until we hand you over to Cley.
Rachel.
The blast door-- I can't get it open.
Why do we always have to fight other people with abilities?
It's annoying.
I guess I'm not meant to be normal, huh? I'm sorry, Bill.
I hoped we'd have more time to talk, but--
you know, weigh the pros and cons
and let you have more time to make your own decision about this.
You know, when you used to talk to me like this, it used to make me cranky.
Well, I'm afraid it will again.
So the decision has been made for me.
How long's it take? Should take effect immediately.
All right, let's give this sucker a test-drive.
Come on, Bill. I can do this. I can do this.
You should be able to by now. The drugs should be kicking in.
Doc, it's not happening. It's not happening.
Look, I'm not sweating, right? My heart rate feels normal.
I'm not feeling any rush or--
- Do you want to? - Of course I want to.
No, that's not what I'm asking you.
What are you saying? You think it's in my head?
Well, your ability to do this has always been linked to an emotional state of yours.
You can't have one without the other.
We are not gonna die because I can't get this up. Well, that should make you angry.
All right, all right, stop. Stop, stop.
Stop. Stop.
You can't do this, all right?
It's okay. Now, we can't find Rachel.
And I think we're going about this the wrong way.
I think we need to go on the offensive.
Are you sure this is going to work? That's it, break up the patterns.
The more abstract the background, the harder it should be for Griffin to blend in.
It's messy. I know Gary, but we're gonna clean it up, Gary, I promise.
Gary, move.
Gary, Gary, move, move.
I am. I am.
Gary, stay right here by-- sit down by that pillar.
Okay, camera's on.
Nina, be careful. You bleeding again?
No, it's fine.
We'll get Rosen to look at it, okay?
Over here. Look behind you.
She's running.
- There! - Where?
Footprints in the creamer.
Gary get in your office. Lock the door.
She's in the MRI room.
Nina, get back here. Where is she?
Where'd she go? It's a trap!
Bill, that door.
Oh my God, Gary. Gary?
Damn it, she's got us.
Gary! Gary! Open up, Gary!
Gary, get to your office and lock the door.
- Gary! - Okay.
Son of a bitch.
Gary! D.C.I.S. don't move!
Stop hiding. Come out.
Open up!
Stop hiding.
Okay, you're only making it worse for yourself.
Just please-- you have to stop hiding.
D.C.I.S. you're under arrest. Stop hiding!
D.C.I.S. you're under arrest now.
- Go to your office! - Please, stop.
You have to stop, please. Stop, please, don't!
- Hey! - No, no.
Oh, that felt so good.
Gary, are you okay?
So how do you do this--
fool our brains so we can't see you?
I've never given it much thought.
Why don't you cut me loose, and we can figure it out together?
I could even give you a demonstration if you'd like.
Didn't think so.
Kern referred to you as an unsanctioned variable.
I prefer Ronin.
Sounds cooler.
I mean, I've been following him for two weeks,
and then you lot scooped him up, so thanks for that.
Why don't you just let me take Kern and leave?
It's the easiest solution to your problem. Well, that's interesting.
He says we should release him to stop you, that you're our problem.
And you don't know who to believe, huh?
You seen your walls lately?
What are you talking about, the cracks?
Yeah, we noticed some cracks on the beams.
There are cracks everywhere.
You got a sonic Alpha in your holding cell.
He's trying to break out of here.
And he's been trying since the minute he woke up.
These vibrations, well...
They take time to build. Yeah, I don't trust her.
For all we know, she's working with Kern.
I'm sorry about the knife, handsome.
See, I don't like it when people get close to me.
I don't like it when they can see me either.
That's why Kern's so annoying--
the sonar. Who are you working for?
Let's just say it's someone that's interested in Kern's research.
His so-called vitamins?
Look, I get paid for delivering Kern's research,
which I've already gotten off your computers.
I get a bonus for bringing in Kern.
I can't do that if I'm dead.
Let's just call a truce. You let me take him out of here.
I get my fee.
You get to live. We all win.
Hicks.
Dr. Rosen, he's bleeding again.
Come with me.
Still bleeding. What's going on?
It's probably the vibrations.
It's okay. It's not like I'm dying or anything.
You don't want Doc here thinking you actually care about me.
Very funny.
Doc, Doc, take a look.
- Look. - Give me this.
Right there.
Oh, my goodness. I can hear the rumbles.
It's getting worse.
Doc.
Doc, I think you need to take a look at him.
I wasn't hurting anyone. Don't make me hurt you.
Whatever happens to us is gonna happen to you.
If you bring this whole building down--
All I wanted was to bring more Alphas into the world.
Why is that wrong? Why are you treating me like a criminal?
Bill, Bill, we've got to get inside there and stop him.
- Here, take this. - What is this?
Ether.
It's not elegant, but it's quick.
It's hot as hell.
He's turned the cell into a reverb chamber.
It's shaking the whole building, and it's creating heat.
The metal might be at the breaking point.
Dr. Rosen!
Duck and cover. Bill, duck and cover.
Gary? Gary, watch her.
Yeah, okay, I'll do both.
I'll watch, and I'll cover. I'll cover us.
He's lost too much blood. We got to get him out of here.
Hicks, come on, come on.
- Take him to the blast door. - Yeah.
I'll find Rosen.
Who hired you?
I was told to bring you in alive, but that's never gonna happen.
It's too late!
So much for my bonus.
You know, a man with your abilities
could make a lot of money
if he went into business for himself.
That's never gonna happen. Yeah?
Well, I owe you one.
And I hate owing people.
So I'll pay you back.
Stanton Parish.
What the hell is that?
You better find out.
Who knew office work was so dangerous, huh?
Stanton Parish?
Yeah, yeah.
It was something that, uh, Griffin threw at me as a parting gift, I guess.
I don't know. Maybe it's a place, a person.
- I don't know. - Well, we'll look into it.
Yeah, well, the sooner the better, Doc.
I told you that we needed gun turrets, Bill.
You know what? I talked to your mother and asked her, could we fight Alphas in your bedroom?
And she said no. What's up with that?
That's not helpful, bill. My house would be the worst place to fight.
And anyway, my bedroom's off-limits. Gary, no, that's a great place.
I think, you know, we can keep them as prisoners there or--
Yeah, yeah, I know what you're trying to do, Bill.
You're trying to annoy me, but it's not gonna work.
You know, you were a lot less annoying when you didn't have your abilities.
And now that you've got your ability back, you're annoying again.
You're Bill again. You're the old Bill. You're damn right I am.
Nina, you don't have to clean up my office.
Yeah, well, don't want your wound to open up.
Rachel would smell blood-- I get it, you like me.
Don't be so, uh... Don't be so juvenile.
Come on, I saw how you reacted when I got cut.
I would've done the same thing to anyone.
Well, how about this?
Now, that's pretty grown-up, huh?
I don't care what Cley says.
This was a bad idea.
Yes, we do seem to be learning by trial and error.
Mostly error.
So no more prisoners in the office, right?
Oh, I certainly hope not, Rachel.
You know, you, uh, saved all of us--
dropping Griffin and detecting Kern's ability.
Just trying to earn my paycheck. I scanned the entire office.
There's no sign of Griffin. She got away.
And I'm assuming that she took the data on Kern's vitamins with her.
She probably delivered it to her new employers, whoever they are.
Things aren't gonna get easier, are they?
破烂熊字幕组
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
欢迎加入
有一个红旗的可能成员来我们办公室了
Cameron说他和Nina已经制服了他
现在他们正要带他来这儿
我想Sullivan会来处理并评估
他是否是个阿尔法 或者跟红旗间有无联系
很显然事情不尽人意
所以我们还是不知道他有什么能力?
对
那么 还好我们来处理这件事了
19 68 16 7
这不是你的生日吧?
第三届超级杯
喷气机队16:7打败了小马队
是啊 但你当时还不够大去看比赛吧
我那时6个月
我见过我爸抱着我看比赛的照片
这样我就成了喷气机队一辈子的铁粉了
而且我们还会去的
去年我们玩的时候你看到了吧?
- 是啊 橄榄球 对吧 Bill?
- 呃 算是吧 橄榄球
总之 我们装了防弹偏振玻璃
工业级电涌抑制器 防火泡沫
最妙的是我们还装了紧急禁闭装置
整个办公室
这样窗户 门 所有东西都被关上
现在我们就差国防部给我们买辆新车了
他们能买吗?
哦 天 Bill 我不知道
这比我以前为咱们设想的过界太多了
医生 你得克服这个观念
我们不再只是你的病人了
我们还是一个政府资产
那句话怎么说来着
在苍白的月色下与魔鬼共舞?
你得顺其自然 好吗
这不是你经常对我说的吗?
听着 自从Jonas Englin的那个烂摊子后
我失去了我的能力 我还在这儿 对吧
我很满意现状 你也很满意 所以...
不 我也不是那么满意的 这不是原来的你
而国防部也不太满意
事实上 我正试着找出能让你能力恢复的办法
你是一个很好的调查员 但在政府眼里
我们是一组阿尔法
可你也不是阿尔法啊 你不还在这儿 对不?
- 而且 医生...
- 呃?
Jeannie和我打算重装厨房
- 所以拜托支票一定不能断
- 这不行
这不行 他们不顾我的清单 我做了一个清单
睡气喷射器 心灵感应阻断器 还有自动炮塔
- Gary 这些东西都不存在
- 是啊 我喜欢以前的Bill多一点
那时你会认真地考虑问题
而当事情不对时 你的静脉就会爆出来
现在就不对
- 为什么你的静脉不再爆出来了
- 我不用再担心这事了
那为什么你还在这儿 你已经不是一个阿尔法了
如果我不在这儿 你会想我的 对不对?
你离开跟你改变是一回事
随便吧 Bill 随你便
我来处理
你们听到我了吗 这是什么噪声?
检查 完毕? Bill 收到吗?
呃 Rachel 这不是警用通信
- 你可以正常说话
- 好吧 我听到他们了
- 他们跟Kern医生一起在电梯里
- 好的 谢谢
抱歉了
能确认跟红旗之间的联系吗?
我们刚坐下他就起疑了
那阿尔法能力呢?
我想要催眠他 但不成功
我想先做磁共振成像检测
接着我们再把他关进牢房里
在他醒过来前赶紧行动吧
医生 你还好吗?
呃 还好 只是...
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==-
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
阿尔法第一季第09集
-=破烂熊字幕组=-
翻译：Moxiran 猫窝 Busy
校对：酒囊饭袋
时间轴：葫芦娃
请不要把他弄醒
放松 Rachel 你知道我还有枪的
我没激动时 准头更好
你知道吗 Bill 我在想
如果我跟你注射肾上腺素和类固醇的混合药物
- 我们也许可以助启你的能力
- 医生 我不想这么做
那个能力总给我惹麻烦 好吗
婚姻的麻烦 工作的麻烦还有...
- 不 我理解你的担心
- 谁需要这种能力呢?
我们可能需要
我们都有自己的麻烦
但我们都在学习如何掌控它们
是啊 现在我一切都尽在掌握中 多谢了
好吧 看看我们找到些什么
报告都做好了 天 你真够积极的
我曾试着忽略它 假装它会消失
但它从未消失过
奶油 不加糖 对不对?
我有留意的
- 我在想是谁把我们的事向Kern告的密
- Guy是个产科医生
他总是见到幸福的一对对
我猜他看不到我们之间的幸福
怎么 我们不能做幸福的一对吗?
不 我不会这么说
Rosen觉得这是个不好的想法
我和你
等等 你告诉他了?
他是我们的心理医生啊
为什么 是不是因为...
因为我离过婚 还在戒酒?
或者是因为我有个小孩
我们在一起工作 这样不专业的
不 我们做这份工作时经常会做些不专业的事
你也知道的
不是这个原因
他认为我对你有坏影响
而且...
他可能是对的
Cam 我搞糟了从前的每一次恋爱
我也是
那我们是绝配咯
嘿 伙计们
呃 医生发现了一些事 我们要开个会
好 我们马上去
- Kern怎么会是瞎的呢?
- 因为他没有视神经
核磁共振展示出了一些非常有意思的事
就好像它们从未发育过一样
所以 即使他的眼睛发育良好
看起来也是如此
但任何视觉数据都无法抵达他的大脑
这就是为什么我无法催眠他 他看不见我
听着 当情况有变时
那男人在桌边闪躲 还直冲到门那边
他不可能是瞎的
除非他是个阿尔法 我对此有些想法
不过我还需要做更多测试
所以我们是在谈一个婴儿医生的盲阿尔法
还可能是红旗一员?
我的电话呢 谁拿了我的电话?
Bill? Bill! Bill!
Gary 我一直在这儿 你在说什么呢?
- 是吗 你把我手机放哪儿了
- Gary 我一直都在你面前
- Gary 你的手机在这儿
- 哦 好吧 这是不对的
人们不该碰我的手机 这是份礼物 这很特别
对 好啦 手机已经回到你手上了
- 没事了
- 不 有事 因为数据文件被打开了 这都是私人资料
是的 Gary的手机是私人物品
请大家都不要碰它 除非得到Gary的许可 好吗?
没错 而且我不会许可的
再说回我们的案子
Kern医生在这儿的原因是...
国防部怀疑他在做某种研究
他们希望我们能找出原因
而且说实话吧 一个激进的阿尔法
同时还是名产科医生 光这个想法就让人不安了
我们清查了他的办公室 硬盘 手机 病人文件
药物 维生素 血液样本
- Rachel 你来看看这些吧
- 好 好极了
Gary 你来查手机和电脑传输?
那是大海捞针 没超能力的人也可以做这个
是啊 你知道的 我们不全能做这事
- 我就做不到 Gary
- 我也不能
不 我们都知道除了超能力外
你还有很多优点 Gary
- 你有很多天赋
- 我知道 我超赞的
今天有得忙了
Gary?
喂?
谁在那儿?
你在叫我吗 我在工作
我的IM聊天状态上写着 勿扰
我该写个牌子的
- 嘿 Gary 你刚去过我办公室吗
- Rachel 你在胡言乱语
我跟你说了 我在工作
我在我办公室工作
- Bill 你能拿掉那堵口带吗
- 你确定?
是的 我拿到我需要的测试结果了
我只想跟他谈谈
好吧 随便你
让我来告诉你 幸福是一支温暖的枪
而我的就是一支西格226 你明白吗?
- 我要找律师
- 是吗 我还想要个鲁宾三明治呢
我会让我的律师给你带一个的
不幸的是 Kern医生 你被拘留
是因为涉嫌参与一个恐怖组织
我所在的唯一组织就是美国医学协会
那什么阿尔法 超能力 红旗
这些词对你来说都没有意义吗?
Bill 你能把那些手铐解开吗
让他站起来 让他的脸对着镜子?
慢慢站起来 手举起来
请转身 对着墙
这是什么意思 检查虫牙啊?
只是我的一个想法...
声纳 回波定位
- 所以说他就像是只蝙蝠
- 或者是一条海豚
你现在可以坐下了
很有意思 你没有视神经
但是 你大脑的音频处理能力
你的喉头
你窦通道的空间
都显著地有所提高 你是个阿尔法
- 当然你已经知道了
- 这事不会有好结果的
这是个威胁吗?
嘿 Cley Rosen和我要继续研究他
Rachel正在查看我们在他办公室找到的东西
是啊 Rosen认为他大概不会再说什么了
所以你们来带走他吧?
好的 两小时?
从Knoxville?
好的 祝你航班顺利哈
- 医生 我们能谈谈吗
- 我有点忙 Cameron 我们能...
不 就一会
听着 我只想说 我和Nina...
如果你能给我们一点空间
让我们自己去理清我们俩的事...
我只是想照看好你们俩人
我明白 但我们都是成年人了
我们得自己犯错 所以拜托 不要插手
我很想 但作为你们的心理医生和雇主
我想我不能这么做
而且我也不认为该由你做这个决定
我打扰你们了吗 我总是打扰人
对不起 但我在箱子里找到些东西
很重要
看这些
"为更好的宝宝而建"
是的 这是给怀孕妇女的维生素
我决定打开一个 看看里面 你明白的
真正地看一看
Rachel 你发现什么了?
DNA...
维生素里面有活性人类DNA
活性人类DNA
注入正在发育中的胎儿的话
会引起多种生产缺陷 严重的突变
是啊 这就是我所担心的
等等 我闻到血的味道...
在走廊里
- Nina
- 刚开始流
我长大之后就再没流过鼻血了
哦 天 往上看 你头晕吗?
- 不 还好
- 有头痛或者其他感觉吗?
只不过破了几条毛细血管
不严重 可你是在挖鼻孔吗?
我不做这事的
来 拿着这个
你会好的 擦干净吧?
好 没事
你知道你有二尖瓣脱垂吗
有三毫米的移位?
你刚给我的胸部做了个超声波
你该去检查下
我每年都会做两次心脏检查的
我在监控它 不过 ...
还是谢谢你的关心了
跟你也一样 我也发过誓...
不害人
- 我也许是个阿尔法 但我首先是个医生
- 我希望你谨记这个想法
不害人
什么样的医生会给怀孕妇女
注入活性人类DNA?
关心未来的人
谁的未来?
你知道Renestrin
那个据说可以抑制生育缺陷的新药吧?
但它实际的作用是
阻碍有更多进化孩子的胚胎发展
你真正想说的是 它阻止了阿尔法的出生吧
把我的特殊维生素想成反作用剂
你计划一个人来分发
你的反作用剂吗?
你的组员有会读心的吗?
那我想 有些事就不会有答案了
Rosen医生 我知道下一步会发生什么
拿着枪的人会把我押送到某个政府建筑里
那将是一个非常非常悲剧的错误
我想真正的悲剧
恐怕是你选择加入一个恐怖组织
红旗并不像你以为的是个庞大的机构
先不说它的范围 你和你的朋友还想要暗杀我
边缘因素 激进派 并不能代表主流
你知道吗 很有意思的是 人们常常使用这个词
"边缘因素"
在我看来 爱尔兰共和军
巴解组织 3K党
所有这些边缘因素
他们的存在都有赖于
他们主流同伴的支持
我读过你的外勤报告 医生
你主张阿尔法和普通人类合作
共建美好未来
这也是我想要的未来
我们本该一起工作 互相学习
你在邀请我加入红旗吗?
恐怕我达不到他们的入门要求吧
我能够预见不久的将来
没有超能力的人也能加入我们的大业
那才是你该待的地方
Kern医生 如果你愿意确切地说出
你想要干什么
我很乐意代表你调停此事
死局
我对你很失望 医生
这个嘛...
我不是要去Binghamton的人
你又怎么会认为去的是我?
Bill? Hicks?
拜托 伙计们 这最好不是在跟我开玩笑
这家伙嘴真紧啊
有办法撬开他的嘴么?
- 像个音速小子
- 是啊
我们该放Captain & Tennille的歌给他听听
麝鼠之爱
- 音速战争
- 嗯
这可是工作中的惯用手法
记住 我们逼他听的东西 我们自己也听得到
相信我 对付巴格拉姆的囚犯我们也这么干过
每次听到科帕卡瓦纳 我还是觉得恶心
- 不过我喜欢那首歌
- 得了吧
真的啊 是我最喜欢的
听见什么了么? Gary又在鼓捣电脑了?
我登不进系统了
好像在进行按键恢复
- 看见Rachel了么?
- 没见过
她不在办公室 有个把钟头都没人看见她了
要不你把她吼出来?
我吼过了 好不好 她不见了
- Rachel?
- Rachel 听见的话就吱一声
- 啥都没有 啥都没有
监视器出问题了
Gary 过来 让我看看你发现了什么
- 接到监视器上
- 好吧 出故障了
回放一小时前Rachel办公室的录像
有东西干扰了监视器
好吧 她在那
在办公室里检查Kern的东西
能快进么?
虽然出故障了 不过应该可以快进
好吧 等等 看这 她走了
等等 找到她了
20分钟前 看这里
在那
Hicks! Nina!
你待在这 跟我来
Rachel!
Rachel?
Rachel 你在哪?
这是监视器最后捕捉到她的地方吧?
- 是的
- Rachel!
- 天啊
- 咋了?
过来
是血
- 这里也有血
- 像是被拖走的痕迹
- 从那里开始拖
- 不 是从这里
她不可能就这么人间蒸发了 搞什么?
Rachel 你在哪? Rachel?
嘿 看看这个
我们搬进来的时候就这样么?
你干了什么?
- Rachel在哪?
- Rachel?
谁是Rachel 高个子的?
- 另一个女人
- 可我见都没见过
你的声纳能力肯定不止找东西
可我被铐在这里了啊
难道我能靠声音绑架别人?
还有 我的听力很好
从我醒过来到现在 这层楼里的心跳声一个没少
那你听到几个心跳声?
你非要跟我玩这么无聊的游戏?
八个 一直是八个心跳声
你的 我的 还有六个我估计是你手下的
尽管你都还没介绍我认识
Kern医生 我们只有六个人 包括Rachel和我
加你 也不过七个
什么?
有没有...
你办公室有没有丢什么东西...
或者听到什么奇怪的声音
电脑无缘无故开机
或者感觉到身边有人 却看不到?
这里来了个不速之客
你是说
Rachel被人绑架了
而绑架她的人还在这幢楼里?
让我来解决 我帮你 不然我们都得死
- 我干嘛要相信你说的?
- 好啊 那就别信
不过你队伍里已经挂了一个了
不听我的 事情只会更糟
让我出去!
趁现在还来得及 让我出去!
你们必须放我出去 只有我能救大家
不用听他的 我一点都不相信他
我把整个办公室搜了个遍 还是找不到Rachel
除了听Kern的 我们别无他法
最好Cley现在就来 把这家伙带走
得等我们把Rachel找到再说
嗯 我觉得我们至少应该判断下Kern说的话
如果真有人潜入 那么发生的一切倒也说得通
医生 今天早些时候
我当时还以为是我的幻觉
我感觉有人在监视我
- 我回过头却发现根本没人
- 正是如此 Bill
这是一种本体感受
是我们的身体处理身边无数信息的
一种方式
就像你说的 如果你置身于一间都是人的房间
你可以感觉到什么
然后你不由自主地转过头 发现有人正看着你
- 这就是因为本体感受
- 那么本体感受说真有人在这
而眼睛却说没有?
差不多吧 和Rachel不同
当我们感受某样东西
我们靠的是视觉
但视觉有时候靠不住
- 你看到几个点?
- 两个
好的 现在你用右手拿着它
闭上左眼
盯着这个点看 慢慢把纸移向你
- 有个点不见了
- 被视觉盲点屏蔽了
你们都听说过盲点 每个人都有
因为视神经在视网膜前穿过
使得视网膜上出现感光缺口
而我们可能碰上了个能利用这点的阿尔法
那好 假设这里真有这么个阿尔法
- 他又是怎么利用盲点的呢?
- Bill 我也不知道
可能是发出一个扩大视神经的信号
借此放大盲点的范围
藏身其中 不被发现
我还是不敢相信 要知道 到处都是探头
阿尔法也许能骗过人 监视器总没办法了吧?
监视器坏了 被人弄坏了
- 有严重的失帧和延迟
- 严重到看都看不到?
是的 不过只有我们的监视器有问题
只是这幢楼里的监视器
街道旁的监视器
每隔15分钟就会扫我们的楼
所以三分钟后我不会去上厕所
- 或者是18 33 或者48分钟后
- Gary Gary Gary 行了
看看这个
等等 这女人是谁
- Hicks 在你背后!
- 跑哪去了?
我看不到她
- Cameron
- Hicks 怎么了?
我都看不到她在哪 情况不妙 好多血
马上拿绷带包住伤口
她关上了隔离门!
密码改了
电话和网络都用不了了
好吧 Rachel失踪 Hicks又受伤
- 就算Cley赶得上 他也进不来
- 不用担心
- Gary应该能破解屏蔽系统
- 值得一试
啊 操蛋的防弹玻璃!
Gary?
- Gary你在干嘛?
- 这次我用两张椅子砸
- Gary 住手
- 刚才我用一张椅子
- 现在用俩
- Gary Gary
不要 Rosen医生 我刚才只用了一张椅子
- 我在跟你说话 Gary
- 让我用两张砸
我需要你帮忙 跟我来好么?
- 我在帮忙
- 来吧
虽然不会致命
不过这几天最好别伸展摸天花板什么的
以前总是Harken负伤
这次我终于也享受被护理的待遇了
好了 行了 我们得去找Rachel
我让Rosen给你弄点药
会上瘾的
不好意思
这样对你不好
我不在乎
那巫婆偷了我的手机
- 什么巫婆?
- 就是那个巫婆!
我妈生气了就会说这个词
有时候也会改个字母(bitch)
带走了Rachel 还拿了我手机
那婊子还拿了我的枪
- 好像是从...
- 听上去像是我的枪
- 防弹玻璃...
- Gary
明智之举
- 要碎了
- Gary
你拿了我的手机? 带走了Rachel?
Gary Gary 去把电脑系统修好
- 盯着他
- 收到
- Cameron 找Rachel
- 交给我了
- 真是我肚子里的蛔虫
- 嘿 她跑哪去了?
盲点女去哪了?
- 你说那个刚对我开枪的人?
- 或者是想放你走的人
我说鸡 你说鸭
我们永远不可能达成相同意见
想要意见相同 不如你先告诉我们她叫什么?
Griffin
她叫Griffin 不过估计不是真名
红旗组织定义其为编外人员
什么意思?
为高报酬才接单行动
但并不隶属于组织
人要有信仰 你觉得呢?
我尊重你们俩 虽然你们误入了歧途
至少你们效忠的原因是伟大的
你是说 她不过是个为钱卖命的雇佣兵?
我的能力对于找到她至关重要
更不要说找你们的伙伴 Rachel
- Rachel 对
- 我可不这么想
然后你们得意洋洋 大摇大摆地走出这里
想得美
我看上去像在耍你们? Griffin是来找我的
为了抓住我她会不择手段
包括把你们全杀了
你不是目标 就是帮凶
不管你是什么 都给我待在这里
直到我们把你交给Cley
Rachel
隔离门 我打不开
为什么我们老是要和些有超能力的人干架?
真蛋疼
- 我永远都做不了正常人 是么?
- 不好意思 Bill
我希望我们能有更多时间聊聊 不过...
权衡利弊
我也希望你能自己做决定
你以前这么跟我说话的时候
我都会觉得很怪
恐怕以后这机会不少
看来我还是"被决定"了
- 多久起效?
- 应该很快
好吧 我来找那家伙过过招
- 用力 Bill
- 我可以的 我可以的
现在你应该可以了 药物应该生效了
医生 不行 我不行
瞧 我满头大汗 心率又很正常
而且也没觉得兴奋或者...
- 你很想?
- 当然想了
我问的不是这个
那是什么? 还是你觉得我没尽全力?
你的能力和你的情绪状态息息相关
两者缺一不可
- 我不把门打开 我们都得死
- 这样想你会发怒的
好了 停下吧
停 停
你抬不起来的
没关系 暂时我们找不到Rachel了
我们可能想错办法了
应该先进攻
- 你觉得这会有用?
- 嗯 喷得越乱越好
背景越抽象 Griffin就越难融入
- 乱七八糟的
- 我知道 Gary 不过之后我们会打扫干净的 我保证
行动 Gary
Gary Gary 行动 动起来
我在 我在做
Gary 就呆在那...坐到柱子旁边
好的 摄像头开了
- Nina 小心点
- 你又流血了?
不 没关系
我们让Rosen来看看好么?
这里 小心身后
她在跑
- 那里!
- 哪里?
乳酪上有足迹
Gary 进你办公室去 锁好门
她在核磁共振室里
- Nina 回来
- 她在哪?
她去了哪?
这是个陷阱!
Bill 那扇门
哦我的天啊 Gary Gary?
该死的 她骗过我们了
Gary! Gary! 打开来 Gary!
Gary 去办公室 把门锁上
- Gary!
- 好啦
狗娘养的
- Gary!
- 我们是DCIS 不要动!
不要躲了 快出来
开门!
别再躲了
好了 你只是在让自己更不利而已
拜托 你真的别再躲了
我们是DCIS
你已经被逮捕了 别躲了!
我们是DCIS 你被逮捕了
- 去你的办公室!
- 拜托 停下
你必须停止 拜托 停下 拜托 不要!
- 嘿!
- 不 不
哦 这感觉真好
Gary 你还好么?
那你是怎么做到的...
瞒过我们的大脑让我们看不见你的?
我从来没多想过这个问题
为什么不帮我松绑
让我们一起来探究一下呢?
如果你愿意的话我甚至能展示给你看
看来你不同意
Kern称你为编外人员
我更喜欢被称为Ronin
听起来比较酷
我已经跟着他两周了
然后你们就把他接手了 真是谢谢了
你怎么就不能让我带上Kern离开呢?
- 这是解决你问题最简单的办法
- 这挺有趣的
他说我们应该释放他来阻止你
你就是我们的问题
你不知道能信任谁 是么?
你最近看过你的墙壁么?
你在说什么 那些裂缝?
是的 我们注意到梁上有些裂缝
到处都有裂缝
你的牢房里关着一个音速阿尔法
他正在试图逃出去
从他醒来的那一刻起一直在尝试
这些震动...
- 可是需要花时间的
- 哦 我不信任她
我们都知道 她和Kern是一伙的
小帅哥 那一刀我很抱歉
你看 我不喜欢别人离我太近
我也不喜欢他们能够看见我
声纳...这就是为什么Kern很烦人
你是谁的手下?
可以说是对Kern的研究感兴趣的某个人
他所谓的维他命?
我只是收钱把Kern的研究送过去
我已经从你的电脑里找到了
如果我把Kern送过去还会有奖金
但如果我死了就拿不到了
我们谈个条件吧 你让我把他带走
我拿到我的钱
你们留下你们的命 双赢
Hicks
Rosen医生 他又流血了
跟我来
还在流血 发生什么了?
可能是因为震动
没事的 又不是说我快死了什么的
你不想让医生认为你真的在关心我吧
真有趣
医生 医生 看一下
- 看
- 给我这个
就在那
- 天啊
- 我都能听见隆隆声了
越来越严重了
医生
医生 我觉得你该看看他
我没伤害任何人 别逼我伤害你
不论我们发生了什么 你也一样
你要是把整栋楼都弄塌了...
我只是想让世界上有更多的阿尔法
这有什么错? 干嘛弄得我像罪犯似的?
Bill Bill 我们要进去阻止他
- 给 带上这个
- 这是什么?
乙醚
可能不太光彩 不过很有效
烫死了
他把牢房变成混响室了
整个房子都在颤 还在产生热量
金属快断了
Rosen医生!
卧倒掩护 Bill 卧倒掩护
Gary? Gary 照顾好她
好 没问题 两样我都能做好
我会照顾她 我也会掩护 我能掩护我们
他失血过多了 我们得带他出去
Hicks 起来 加油
- 把他带到屏蔽门那儿去
- 好
我去找Rosen
谁雇你的?
本来我该把你活着带去的 但不可能了
太迟了!
我的奖金这下没了
你知道 一个拥有你这样能力的人
是能赚很多钱的
如果他能好好开发自己的话
- 绝不可能
- 是么?
好吧 我欠你份人情
而我很讨厌欠别人
所以我会回报你
Stanton Parish
什么意思?
你最好查出来
谁能想到办公室工作也能这么危险呢?
Stanton Parish?
没错 是的
Griffin给我的什么临别礼物 我猜
不知道 也许是个地方 也许是个人
- 我不知道
- 我们会去调查的
好的 越快越好 医生
Bill 我跟你说过我们需要炮塔
你知道么? 我和你妈妈谈过
并且问她我们能不能在你房间与阿尔法斗争?
她说不行 这为什么?
没用的 Bill 我的房子不适合
- 再说 我的卧室是禁地
- Gary 别 那地方棒极了
我觉得我们能把他们
作为犯人一直关在那或者...
好了 好了 我明白你的小心思 Bill
你在试图烦我 但没用的
你知道 你失去能力之后一点都不烦人
但现在你重新获得能力了
就又开始烦人了
- 你又是Bill了 原来的那个Bill
- 你说的太他妈对了
Nina 你没必要清理我的办公室
是的 我只是不想你的伤口又裂开
- Rachel会闻到血的味道的...
- 我明白了 你喜欢我
别这么 呃...别幼稚了
得了 我受伤的时候看到你有多紧张了
谁受伤了我都这样
那这个怎么解释?
这够成熟了哈?
我不在乎Cley怎么说
这可不是好主意
是的 我们似乎总是
从实验和错误中吸取经验
大部分是错误
所以不再把犯人放办公室了吧?
我当然希望不了 Rachel
你知道 你 呃 救了我们大家...
干倒Griffin 发现Kern的能力
只是混口饭吃罢了 我检查了整个办公室
没有Griffin的迹象 她走了
我猜她还带走了Kern的维他命上的数据
也许带去给她的新雇主了吧 管他是谁
总是没法省心 不是么?
破烂熊字幕组
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
欢迎加入